unifiedpost.com 2019-05-31

# PRIVACY COOKIE POLICY - UnifiedPost

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.

You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the Site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

_**Note** : the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites._

## Collection of Information

We only collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.

The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request as well as for direct marketing purposes subject to the legitimate interest of this website.

The processing and use of the collected information takes place in a member state of the European Economic area. Any data transfer of processing to a third country shall be subject to the prior approval of the Controller.

## Cookie and Tracking Technology

The Site uses cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors.

Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

## Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.  
​

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure.

Unified Post ensures to have implemented the technical and organizational measures to protect personal information in accordance with the requirements of the GDPR directive 2016/679

Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this Site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

## Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: [gdpr@unifiedpost.com](mailto:gdpr@unifiedpost.com)
